

CONTACT



+90 542 190 6213



Emre Mert



EmreMrt



Web Developer



Makro Beyin



Selcuklu / Konya

HARD SKILLS

- Self Improvement
- Result Focus
- Strategic Management
- Critical Thinking
- Efficiency
- Planning

SOFT SKILLS

- Leading
- Persuasive Ability
- Self Confidence
- Developing Others

COMPUTER SKILLS

- C Programming
- Html5
- Css3
- Boostrap
- Javascript
- React.js
- Node.js MongoDB

LANGUAGES

Turkish English





EMRE MERT

COMPUTER SCIENCE

ABOUT

I have so curious, and researcher personality, so I am learning anything fast. I enjoy teaching it others. For this reason, I am sure, if we work together, I will add value your company and your employee. I will learn new information while you add experience to me. Therefore, we will grow up together.

WORK EXPERIENCE

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

Freelance | 2022 - Present

- I will design a website using Html Css Javascript Boostrap4 -
- Cat-Fellaz project created by me. I have shared the source code privately on Github. catfellaz.com

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

Dostext | 2022 - Present

- This project is about disabled people so I am a volunteer
- I will design a website using Html Css Javascript Boostrap -Jauerv

EMBEDDED SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Ornek Automation and Robotic Systems | 2021 - 2022

- I am coding a autonomous agricalture machine with STM32F407VG
- I am learning stepping, DC motor control and also M542 motor control driver and encoder
- I am generally working with ADC, DAC, PWM and Bluetooth Sensors
- I will learn UART and USART protocols and also CAN

EDUCATION

COMPUTER SCIENCE

University of Selcuk | Present GPA 3.27

ELECTRIC

University of Cukuroval 2018 GPA 2.88

ELECTRIC AND ELECTRONIC

Technical and Vocations High School | 2016 GPA 3.4

AWARDS

S C H O O L CL U B

HIGH HONOR STUDENT Selcuk University | 2021

TARGET | Leader of Community Selcuk University | 2021

REFERENCE

VOLUNTEER

Assoc. Prof. Dr. Humar KAHRAMANLI ÖRNEK | Co-Head of department Selcuk University | hkahramanli@selcuk.edu.tr

TEGV | 2019 - 2020

- I teached Scratch for children (12 years old)
- I mentioned relationship between software and hardware

Dr. Mustafa Nevzat ÖRNEK | Academician - Founder Ornek Automation and Robotic Systems | mnornek@ktun.edu.tr

PROJECT

EMBEDDED SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Target SÜ Robotaxi Team | 2021 - 2022

- Found and managed project and team membership.
- I am coding control and protection card with C programming at ESP32 and Arduino Mega microcontroller.
- I am working ARM architecture, communication protocols (SPI, I2C, UART)

EMBEDDED SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Target Techdown Rocket Team | 2021 - 2022

- I am coding 2nd control card with C programming at STM32F100 series microcontroller.
- I am working ARM architecture, communication protocol (UART) using with Hal Library and peripheral's library at STM32.
- My goal is to communicate from rocket to ground station and also, the rocket can flies over 3000 ft we will
 open parachute.

EMBEDDED HARDWARE DESIGNER

Target Robotaxi Team | 2020 - 2021

- I have designed control and protection card at Eagle Cad.
- I have coded and tested protection card such as voltage, current, temprature, IR sensors and cooler fan drivers (ECU) at Atmega2560.
- I have had to learn very much sensors and coded with microcontroller in real project.

LICENCE&CERTIFICATION

- Professional C Programming | UDEMY | 2021
- Pearson Assured | Pearson | 2020
- English Lesson | IIENSTITU | 2020